{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Composite Deck Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/62554/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62554,"taskName":"Composite Deck - Build or Replace","taskDescription":"Build or Replace a Composite Deck","xmTaskDescriptor":"Composite Deck Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"deck porch composite vinyl plastic fake wood faux-wood","textMessagingName":"Composite Deck","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes deck surfaces, railings \u0026 associated stairs \u0026 landings.","rolloverShortDesc":"Deck materials include artificial woods.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Build or Replace a Composite Deck.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated deck contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Composite Decking Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install or Replace a Composite Deck","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":17,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Composite Deck Build or Replace","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Composite Deck - Build or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Composite Deck Project","urlName":"Composite-Deck-Build","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Composite Deck Builders \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Composite Decking Installation","searchKeywords":"deck porch composite vinyl plastic fake wood faux-wood","emcCategoryOid":-12017,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9193,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62554/":{"taskOID":62554,"originalTaskOID":62554,"setID":9193,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4607,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200674,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Build or replace a deck","answerDisplayText":"Build or replace a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair an existing deck","answerDisplayText":"Repair an existing deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6269,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you would like:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8411,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in benches","answerDisplayText":"Built-in benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","answerDisplayText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom railings","answerDisplayText":"Custom railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8414,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Planters/Storage boxes","answerDisplayText":"Planters/Storage boxes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8415,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Multi-level deck","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8416,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screened-in deck","answerDisplayText":"Screened-in deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8417,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electrical features","answerDisplayText":"Electrical features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8418,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hot tub/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Hot tub/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8419,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Waterproof to protect area below","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof to protect area below","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8420,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Built-in barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Built-in barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6909,"questionDisplayText":"What size deck or porch do you want?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size deck or porch do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9981,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9982,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9983,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4607,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":200674,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Build or replace a deck","answerDisplayText":"Build or replace a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair an existing deck","answerDisplayText":"Repair an existing deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200674,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Build or replace a deck","answerDisplayText":"Build or replace a deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200675,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repair an existing deck","answerDisplayText":"Repair an existing deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6269,"questionDisplayText":"Special Features","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select any special features you would like:","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8411,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in benches","answerDisplayText":"Built-in benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","answerDisplayText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom railings","answerDisplayText":"Custom railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8414,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Planters/Storage boxes","answerDisplayText":"Planters/Storage boxes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8415,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Multi-level deck","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8416,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screened-in deck","answerDisplayText":"Screened-in deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8417,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electrical features","answerDisplayText":"Electrical features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8418,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hot tub/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Hot tub/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8419,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Waterproof to protect area below","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof to protect area below","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8420,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Built-in barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Built-in barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8411,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Built-in benches","answerDisplayText":"Built-in benches","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8412,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","answerDisplayText":"Pergola/Arbor/Patio Cover","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8413,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Custom railings","answerDisplayText":"Custom railings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8414,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Planters/Storage boxes","answerDisplayText":"Planters/Storage boxes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8415,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Multi-level deck","answerDisplayText":"Multi-level deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8416,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Screened-in deck","answerDisplayText":"Screened-in deck","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8417,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Electrical features","answerDisplayText":"Electrical features","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8418,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hot tub/Spa","answerDisplayText":"Hot tub/Spa","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8419,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Waterproof to protect area below","answerDisplayText":"Waterproof to protect area below","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8420,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Built-in barbeque","answerDisplayText":"Built-in barbeque","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":6909,"questionDisplayText":"What size deck or porch do you want?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What size deck or porch do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9981,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9982,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9983,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9981,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Small (less than 150 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9982,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Medium (150 - 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9983,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","answerDisplayText":"Large (more than 300 sq ft)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}